Rhinedottir... something's wrong...
We're not done. You're not going anywhere
Pierro...!
Just in time...
Though it's never been tested in live combat...
At least the "Eye of the Fatui" was completed in time
You should not be able to wield that power...
No mortal body or mind can withstand it
Even with my Curse of Immortality...
The Fatui do not care
For the right to gaze upon the gods
Whatever the price may be, whatever I must suffer, so be it!
Nice job, Eftirvit
That is enough!
Watch out, here it comes again...
Not again... I thought we'd have more time...
Come on... I have to get back... before it's too late!
Faster... Faster!
You...!
It all makes sense now...
The six Gnoses you collected...
It was all to deal with me
I'm surprised
With Cryo energy maximally enhanced by the Gnoses
You can affect the bounds of Reason...
Not enough to completely freeze space and time
But enough to slow down the flow of time where we are...
Am I wrong, Cryo Archon?